<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on NaNoWriMo 2019</title>
    <link>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on NaNoWriMo 2019</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Opening Image (0-1%)</title>
      <link>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/01a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/01a/</guid>
      <description>Opens with main character peeking behind stage curtain; watches as another actor begins walking towards her and moves out on the screen. The lights are bright, but she can see a normal attendee sitting out in the crowd, a small red light in his hand. She smiles, knowing he has been in this scene before and wonders how it will go differently. She recalls before when he had not known the outcome and chose to use the shot from the medkit on the alien visitor, killing him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theme Stated (5%)</title>
      <link>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/01b-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/01b-theme/</guid>
      <description>As she contemplates the man who acted again (is he important?), she also reminisces on her father and sister. How he had been supportive until ? and then once his sister went to school to study space, had lost interest in her own wellbeing.
She considers that her sister hasn&amp;rsquo;t texted her yet, and although she knows something is wrong, she puts off calling her father. (She has often put off important feelings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set-up (1%-10%) </title>
      <link>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/01c-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/01c-setup/</guid>
      <description>Still believing something is wrong but not sure how to confront it, she goes to work the next day (Friday) and tells coworkers she will be on leave for awhile. One of her coworkers/friend asks to take her to coffee. (Anxious, she discusses a lost trinket she&amp;rsquo;s kept from an audience member.)
Quip about there still being long lines for coffee. After talking with a friend&amp;ndash;possibly about the sister history in the theme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catalyst (10%)</title>
      <link>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/01d-catalyst/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/01d-catalyst/</guid>
      <description>Father answers and tells her that her sister has been in an accident and died. Father reminds her that she is the lesser of the two.
Goes home to meet w/ her father; fighting and confusion about vagueness of her sister&amp;rsquo;s death.
Maybe she finds a piece of paper/receipt of a payout for the death of her sister.
The space team requests that the main character come to pick up her sister&amp;rsquo;s personal effects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debate (10%-20%)</title>
      <link>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/01e-debate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/01e-debate/</guid>
      <description>Angry that the man was focused on her space knowledge and not her acting skills, she leaves dinner at the fancy place. He says the same: &amp;ldquo;if you had wanted to go into acting, you&amp;rsquo;ve already passed up those opportunities.&amp;rdquo;
Near the exit, she is recognized by a random man who suggests she audition for a role w/ a “star actor.” Eager to make a point, she agrees to stop by auditions next week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Break into Two (20%) </title>
      <link>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/02a-break2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/02a-break2/</guid>
      <description>She decided to go to the audition instead.
As she makes her way to the audition, she is kidnapped by a van in front of the audition area (which wasn’t really the audition spot.)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>B Story (22%)</title>
      <link>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/02b-bstory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/02b-bstory/</guid>
      <description>She often talks with her guard/kidnapper’s assistant. He was in a play with her when they were younger, but he took a wrong turn in life. His acting skills come in handy as he pretends to be another prisoner, but since they know eachother, it doesn’t quite work. They discuss each other’s lives (his are mostly lies) and he tells her “Now you’ve got that fame you wanted,” as he shows her that her photo is on the news.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Promise of the Premise (20%-50%)</title>
      <link>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/02c-premise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/02c-premise/</guid>
      <description>After her dad pays the ransom, their father/daughter relationship improves. She realizes it is safe but it could happen again. She is fearful of finding another acting opportunity and attempts to resume being a STEM instructor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Midpoint (50%) </title>
      <link>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/02d-midpoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/02d-midpoint/</guid>
      <description>She receives notes encouraging her to go into space. She also thinks back on her kidnapper and wonders what is happening to him. Where does the money go, and how can he get out of the lifestyle?
This is the first time you’ve thought about someone other than yourself.
She tries to meet w/ her kidnapper guy again, but she isn’t able to reach him. She plays with the trinket and realizes there is a secret compartment with a photo of the boy in front of his old house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bad Guys Close In (50%-75%) </title>
      <link>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/02e-badguys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/02e-badguys/</guid>
      <description>The boy’s mother gives her a call and tells her that he agreed to meet with her. She’s excited, but anxious.
When she goes to a local shop, she sees an older photo of her swim team with the swim team and her (coach). The man does not look the same as she had remembered.
They meet for coffee, but he tells her that it was a mistake and that he shouldn’t ever be involved in her life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All is Lost (75%-80%)</title>
      <link>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/02f-alllost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/02f-alllost/</guid>
      <description>She meets with her love interest secretly, but as they leave she is confronted by the original kidnapper. Trying to protect her, the love interest is shot. She runs to his mom who grieves and asks her to leave. Devastated, she auditions for a play once again, but realizes that the joy of stardom has left her. She wishes that she could still go to space, but the deadline has passed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark Night of the Soul (75%-80%) </title>
      <link>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/02g-dark/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/02g-dark/</guid>
      <description>She grieves. She receives another letter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Break into Three (80%)</title>
      <link>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/03a-break3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/03a-break3/</guid>
      <description>She wants to be part of something greater than herself, and so she decides to finally make the leap and go to the space station. Lots of paperwork and confidentiality.
She looks back at the trinket of the smiling boy and thinks about what he had said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finale (80%-99%) </title>
      <link>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/03b-finale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/03b-finale/</guid>
      <description>Asks to give the audience member acting skills. Watch for cues, etc.
Fools the kidnapper by using her acting skills along with the help from the audience member/actor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Final Image (99%-100%)</title>
      <link>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/03c-finalscene/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/03c-finalscene/</guid>
      <description>One last thing—those notes&amp;hellip; weren&amp;rsquo;t from your sister. (They were originally written by your grandmother)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>