<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on NaNoWriMo 2019</title>
    <link>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on NaNoWriMo 2019</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Opening Image (0-1%)</title>
      <link>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/01a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/01a/</guid>
      <description>Performing in a play; ends/enjoys applause. She has been working hard to leave her job and live a life acting in the big leagues. Receives a call/text about her bro; expecting congrats, she is devastated</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theme Stated (5%)</title>
      <link>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/01b-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/01b-theme/</guid>
      <description>Flashback: her brother tells her “you was great, but destined for something even greater than herself”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set-up (1%-10%) </title>
      <link>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/01c-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/01c-setup/</guid>
      <description>Goes to work the next day (Friday) and tells coworkers she will be on leave for awhile. Flashback to earlier performances where her brother rooted her on. She dreams of being famous. Goes home to meet w/ her father; fighting and confusion about her brother and the vague way he died. Returns home to partake in more plays, enjoys the play but realizes there’s no message on her phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catalyst (10%)</title>
      <link>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/01d-catalyst/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/01d-catalyst/</guid>
      <description>Meets an adoring fan, with an “opportunity” and asks to take her to dinner. Anxious, she discusses the trinket with another play member from a past relationship. Goes to dinner. Referred from her father, the “fan” asks if she’d be interested in a space mission. Her brother had always spoke so highly of her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debate (10%-20%)</title>
      <link>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/01e-debate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/01e-debate/</guid>
      <description>Angry, she leaves dinner at the fancy place, and outside she is recognized by a random person who suggests she audition for a role w/ a “star actor.” She agrees to stop by auditions next week. Discusses w/ friend about her brother. Suggested that this could be her “biggest part yet!” Thinking of the fame and glory, she tentatively accepts. Later, she is phoned the time/place and finds out the audition try-outs are the same time as the orientation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Break into Two (20%) </title>
      <link>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/02a-break2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/02a-break2/</guid>
      <description>She decided to go to the audition instead.
As she makes her way to the audition, she is kidnapped by a van in front of the audition area (which wasn’t really the audition spot.)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>B Story (22%)</title>
      <link>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/02b-bstory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/02b-bstory/</guid>
      <description>She often talks with her guard/kidnapper’s assistant. He was in a play with her when they were younger, but he took a wrong turn in life. His acting skills come in handy as he pretends to be another prisoner, but since they know eachother, it doesn’t quite work. They discuss each other’s lives (his are mostly lies) and he tells her “Now you’ve got that fame you wanted,” as he shows her that her photo is on the news.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Promise of the Premise (20%-50%)</title>
      <link>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/02c-premise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/02c-premise/</guid>
      <description>After her dad pays the ransom, their father/daughter relationship improves. She realizes it is safe but it could happen again. She is fearful of finding another acting opportunity and attempts to resume being a STEM instructor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Midpoint (50%) </title>
      <link>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/02d-midpoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/02d-midpoint/</guid>
      <description>She receives notes encouraging her to go into space. She also thinks back on her kidnapper and wonder what is happening to him. Where does the money go, and how can he get out of the lifestyle? This is the first time you’ve thought about someone other than yourself. She tries to meet w/ her kidnapper guy again, but she isn’t able to reach him. She plays with the trinket and realizes there is a secret compartment with a photo of the boy in front of his old house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bad Guys Close In (50%-75%) </title>
      <link>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/02e-badguys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/02e-badguys/</guid>
      <description>The boy’s mother gives her a call and tells her that he agreed to meet with her. She’s excited, but anxious. They meet for coffee, but he tells her that it was a mistake and that he shouldn’t ever be involved in her life. It is a risk for everyone. She’s sure they can make it work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All is Lost (75%-80%)</title>
      <link>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/02f-alllost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/02f-alllost/</guid>
      <description>She meets with her love interest secretly, but as they leave she is confronted by the original kidnapper. Trying to protect her, the love interest is shot. She runs to his mom who grieves and asks her to leave. Devastated, she auditions for a play once again, but realizes that the joy of stardom has left her. She wishes that she could still go to space, but the deadline has passed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark Night of the Soul (75%-80%) </title>
      <link>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/02g-dark/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/02g-dark/</guid>
      <description>She grieves. She receives another letter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Break into Three (80%)  </title>
      <link>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/03a-break3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/03a-break3/</guid>
      <description>She wants to be part of something greater than herself, and so she decides to finally make the leap and go to the space station. Lots of paperwork and confidentiality.
She looks back at the trinket of the smiling boy and thinks about what he had said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finale (80%-99%) </title>
      <link>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/03b-finale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/03b-finale/</guid>
      <description>You will not be able to return. And… we will have to kill you off. She considers those around me: “It’s okay, I’ve had enough fame for my lifetime.”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Final Image (99%-100%)</title>
      <link>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/03c-finalscene/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://virtual.github.io/nanowrimo19/beatsheet/03c-finalscene/</guid>
      <description>“One last thing—those notes, they’re from your brother.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>